Guide to the Robert J. Levine Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1953-1997; Series I
  - Livingston, Matthew, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 430)
  - LiVolsi, Virginia, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 431)
  - Livstone, Elliot, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 432)
  - Longnecker, David, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 433)
  - Lord, Benjamin, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 434)
  - Louis, Thomas, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 435)
  - Louisell, David, 1975, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 436)
  - Love, Dorothy, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 437)
  - Lowe, Charles, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 438)
  - Lowenstein, Edward, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 439)
  - Lown, Bernard, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 440)
  - Lowry, Oliver H., 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 441)
  - Lubbers, Jeffrey, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 442)
  - Lurie, Irwin, Undated (Box 4, Folder 443)
  - Lurie, Nicole, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 444)
  - Luzzatto, L., 1973 (Box 4, Folder 445)
  - Lynch, Janice M., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 446)
  - Macaraeg, Placido, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 447)
  - Madeira, Nancy Powell, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 448)
  - MaGuire, Nancy, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 449)
  - Maher, John, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 450)
  - Maiman, Lois, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 451)
  - Maloney, James, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 452)
  - Mandel, H. George, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 453)
  - Mandeville, John, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 454)
  - Marburger, John H., 1984 (Box 4, Folder 455)
  - Maren, Thomas, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 456)
  - Marin, Josephina, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 457)
  - Marini, James, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 458)
  - Marks, Bernard, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 459)
  - Marks, Jay, 1969-1974 (Box 4, Folder 460)
  - Mathews, Christopher, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 461)
  - Maudsley, David, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 462)
  - Maxwell, Robert, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 463)
  - May, Burkard, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 464)
  - McCallum, Richard, 1981, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 465)
  - McConkie, Jim, Undated (Box 4, Folder 466)
  - McEwen, Charles, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 467)
  - McFarlane, Michael, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 468)
  - McGeehan, Jude, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 469)
  - McGuigan, James, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 470)
  - McKim, Robert, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 471)
  - McLeod, L. E., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 472)
  - McQuade, John F., 1972 (Box 4, Folder 473)
  - Medical Letter, 1967-1970, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 474-475)
  - Medical Opinion and Review, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 476)
  - Meier, Levi, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 477)
  - Meilin, Bill, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 478)
  - Mellinger, Glen, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 479)
  - Mellinkoff, Sherman, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 480)
  - Men of Achievement, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 481)
  - Mendlowitz, Milton, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 482)
  - Mengel, Charles, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 483)
  - Messer, Joseph V., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 484)
  - Meyer, Harriet, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 485)
  - Meyers, Bruce F., 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 486)
  - Meyers, Olive, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 487)
  - Mezritz, Marjorie, Circa 1975 (Box 4, Folder 488)
  - Michaelson, I. Arthur, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 489)
  - Migliardi, Joseph, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 490)
  - Miller, Batya, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 491)
  - Mirkin, Bernard, 1968-1981 (Box 5, Folder 492)
  - Misher, Allen, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 493)
  - Mitchell, William, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 494)
  - Mittal, Kavi, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 495)
  - Monagle, John F., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 496)
  - Montana, University of, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 497)
  - Morgan, Thomas, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 498)
  - Morrell, Michael, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 499)
  - Morris, Scott, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 500)
  - Motoyama, Etsuro K., 1982 (Box 5, Folder 501)
  - Mudgil, Latta, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 502)
  - Mulcahy, Edwin C., 1984 (Box 5, Folder 503)
  - Mulrow, P. J., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 504)
  - Munson, Paul, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 505)
  - Murphy, Edmond A., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 506)
  - Murphy, Tim, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 507)
  - Murray, Patricia, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 508)
  - Nandi, Manis, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 509)
  - National Forum, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 510)
  - Neal, Heather, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 511)
  - Neek, Robert, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 512)
  - Nejelski, Paul, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 513-514)
  - Nelson, Marjorie, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 515)
  - Nelson, William, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 516)
  - Nevins, Madeline, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 517)
  - New, Maria, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 518)
  - Newman, Andy, 1974-1982 (Box 5, Folder 519)
  - New Mexico, University of, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 520)
  - Nguyen, Nicolas, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 521)
  - Nilges, Richard, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 522)
  - Noll, Walter, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 523)
  - Nolte, Hartmut, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 524)
  - Norburg, Arthur, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 525)
  - Nordlund, James, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 526)
  - Norton, Martin L., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 527)
  - Nottingham, Stuart, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 528)
  - Novick, Gina, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 529)
  - Nugent, Frank T., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 530)
  - O'Brien, William, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 531)
  - Ogden, John, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 532)
  - Oleson, Virginia, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 533)
  - Olson, Hardin E., 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 534)
  - Olson, William A., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 535)
  - Oppelt, W. Walter, 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 536)
  - Ostashever, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 537)
  - Oster, Kurt, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 538)
  - O'Sullivan, Gwen, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 539)
  - Oxford University Press, 1969, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 540)
  - Page, Benjamin, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 541)
  - Page, Irma, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 542)
  - Palenik, G. J., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 543)
  - Palmer, Henry, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 544)
  - Papper, Solomon, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 545)
  - Parthum, Charles, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 546)
  - Passareti, Toni, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 547)
  - Pastides, Harris, Undated (Box 5, Folder 548)
  - Patel, N. C., 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 549)
  - Patterson, Laird, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 550)
  - Pearson, John, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 551)
  - Peck, Richard L., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 552)
  - Peltier, David, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 553)
  - Perdue, Henry, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 554)
  - Peterson, Malcolm, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 555)
  - Pettinger, William A., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 556)
  - Pfeiffer, B. Victor, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 557)
  - Pfeiffer, Carl J., 1970 (Box 5, Folder 558)
  - Phair, John, 1967-1974 (Box 5, Folder 559)
  - Phillips, Herbert, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 560)
  - Piemme, Thomas, 1969-1981 (Box 5, Folder 561)
  - Pietrangelo, René, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 562)
  - Piggott, Leonard R., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 563)
  - Pines, Marcia, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 564)
  - Pispati, P. K., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 565)
  - Poffenbarger, Phillip, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 566)
  - Pool, Ithiel de Sola, 1979, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 567)
  - Porte, Daniel, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 568)
  - Prager, David, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 569)
  - Pratt, Peter W., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 570)
  - Pritzker, Mark, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 571)
  - Prosnitz, Leonard, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 572)
  - Putman, Charles, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 573)
  - Quinn, James J., S. J., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 574)
  - Rafaelsen, Ole, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 575)
  - Rahmoeller, Glenn, Undated (Box 5, Folder 576)
  - Rahn, K. Heinz, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 577)
  - Raisz, Larry, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 578)
  - Rammelkamp, Charles H., 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 579)
  - Redlich, F. C., 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 580)
  - Rees, Roberts M., Undated (Box 5, Folder 581)
  - Regelson, William, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 582)
  - Reilly, Margaret A., 1968-1977 (Box 5, Folder 583)
  - Renkin, Barbara Z., 1979 (Box 5, Folder 584)
  - Renold, Albert, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 585)
  - Reynolds, Paul, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 586)
  - Richards, Frederic M., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 587)
  - Richards, William R., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 588)
  - Rimer, Barbara, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 589)
  - Ringler, Ira, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 590)
  - Ringold, Evelyn, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 591)
  - Ritschel, W. A., 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 592)
  - Roberts, David H., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 593)
  - Roberts, John, Circa 1974 (Box 6, Folder 594)
  - Robinson, Donald S., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 595)
  - Robison, G. Alan, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 596)
  - Rocco, Frank, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 597)
  - Rock, Miriam, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 598)
  - Rogers, David E., 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 599)
  - Rolnick, Michael, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 600)
  - Romano, John, 1975-1982 (Box 6, Folder 601)
  - Rosa, Robert, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 602)
  - Rose-Grippa, Kathy, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 603)
  - Rosen, Jonathan, Undated (Box 6, Folder 604)
  - Rosen, Saul W., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 605)
  - Rosner, Gary, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 606)
  - Ross, A. F., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 607)
  - Ross, Stephen, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 608)
  - Rossi, Joseph, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 609)
  - Roth, Harold, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 610-611)
  - Roth, Jesse, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 612)
  - Roth, Lloyd, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 613)
  - Rothbart, Robert, 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 614)
  - Rothstein, Peter, 1977, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 615)
  - Rowe, Kenneth W., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 616)
  - Rubin, Bernard, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 617)
  - Rubin, Philip, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 619)
  - Rudman, Daniel, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 620)
  - Rubin, Cyrus, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 618)
  - Ruiz Santana, Francisco H., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 621)
  - Sabatino, Frank, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 622)
  - Saber, Fay, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 623-624)
  - Sachdev, Jagdish, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 625)
  - Sachs, David P., 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 626)
  - Sadler, Alfred M., 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 627)
  - St. John, Ronald, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 628)
  - Saintonge, D. Mark C. de, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 629)
  - Salladay, Susan A., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 630)
  - Sanderson, Helen, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 631)
  - Sandler, Merton, 1967, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 632)
  - Sandling, Juli, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 633)
  - Sanford, Jay P., 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 634)
  - Sather, Mike, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 635)
  - Sawchuk, Steven, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 636)
  - Sawyer, Robert, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 637)
  - Schaffner, William, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 638)
  - Schayer, Richard W., 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 639)
  - Schenk, Worthington G., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 640)
  - Schiffrin, M. J. (Red), 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 641)
  - Schildkraut, Joseph, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 642)
  - Schiller, Carol, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 643)
  - Schimmel, Elihu, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 644)
  - Schmidt, Charles E., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 645)
  - Schneckloth, Roland E., 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 646)
  - Schneider, Bryan, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 647)
  - Schnitman, Paul, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 648)
  - Schreiber, Melvyn H., 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 649)
  - Schroeder, Steven, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 650)
  - Schulz, Pierre, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 651)
  - Schumacher, Michael J., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 652)
  - Schuster, Annie Lee, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 653)
  - Schwartz, A. Herbert, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 654)
  - Schwartz, William, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 655)
  - Schwitzgebel, Robert, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 656)
  - Scott, David T., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 657)
  - Scott, John Porter, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 658)
  - Scurlock, Reagan, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 659)
  - Seamon, Barbara, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 660)
  - Seibert, Charles, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 661)
  - Seichter, Marilyn, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 662)
  - Seligson, David, 1981-1987 (Box 6, Folder 663)
  - Senn, Milton, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 664)
  - Sessoms, Rose, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 665)
  - Sethy, Vimala, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 666-667)
  - Severin, Matthew, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 668)
  - Shearman, D. J. C., 1965-1970 (Box 6, Folder 669)
  - Shepherd, Dorothy, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 670)
  - Sheps, Cecil G., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 671)
  - Sherman, Barry, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 672)
  - Sherman, John, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 673)
  - Sherwin, Roger, Undated (Box 6, Folder 674)
  - Sheth, U. K., 1969-1974 (Box 6, Folder 675)
  - Shideman, F. E., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 676)
  - Shih, Pin-Ling, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 677)
  - Shore, Parkhurst A., 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 678)
  - Shuttee, Wayne, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 679)
  - Silver, George, 1972, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 680)
  - Simenhoff, Michael, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 681)
  - Singleton, John, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 682)
  - Skinner, B. F., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 683)
  - Smid, Henk, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 684)
  - Smith, H. Daniel, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 685)
  - Smith, Lloyd, 1970, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 687)
  - Smith, McFate, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 686)
  - Smith, Regina, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 688)
  - Smith, Robert V., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 689)
  - Smolker, Rosemary, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 690)
  - Snyder, Solomon, 1965-1971 (Box 6, Folder 691)
  - Spencer, Richard, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 692)
  - Spierra, Harry, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 693)
  - Spinka, Harold, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 694)
  - Staffier, John, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 695)
  - Stanley, Michael, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 696)
  - Stark, Bennett, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 697)
  - Stein, Jane, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 698)
  - Stein, Martin, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 699)
  - Steinberg, Daniel, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 700)
  - Steiner, George, 1970-1977 (Box 6, Folder 701)
  - Steinfels, Margaret, 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 702)
  - Stern, Aaron, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 703)
  - Stevens, Amy, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 704)
  - Stevenson, Joanne S., 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 705)
  - Stolman, Cynthia, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 706)
  - Storer, Edward, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 707)
  - Stroh, Veronika, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 708)
  - Stuetz, Bernie, 1975-1980 (Box 6, Folder 709)
  - Stump, Emmaline, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 710)
  - Sumner, Kenneth, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 711)
  - Sundaresan, P. R., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 712)
  - "Survival Book", 1982 (Box 6, Folder 713)
  - Swain, Barbara, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 714)
  - Swigar, Mary, Circa 1975 (Box 6, Folder 715)
  - Tabachnick, Irving I. A., 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 716)
  - Tagamet: Placebo Panel, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 717)
  - Takagi, Hiroshi, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 718)
  - Talalla, Andrew, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 719)
  - Talley, Robert, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 720)
  - Tannenbaum, Philip J., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 721)
  - Tanzer, Jason, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 722)
  - Tapley, Caroline, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 723)
  - Tarantino, Michael, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 724)
  - Tashjian, Armen, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 725)
  - Tavares, Brenildo, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 726)
  - Taylor, Charles, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 727)
  - Taylor, Nancy, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 728)
  - Teagar, Bruce N., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 729)
  - Telford, Gordon, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 730)
  - Teplitsky, Benjamin, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 731)
  - Thayer, Walter, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 732)
  - Theriault, Elayne, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 733)
  - Thomas, Joseph, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 734)
  - Thomas, Micki, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 735)
  - Thompson, James C., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 736)
  - Thompson, Jeremy, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 737)
  - Thompson, Lawrence, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 738)
  - Thorn, George, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 739)
  - Throne, Martin L., 1971 (Box 7, Folder 740)
  - Tilghman, Joseph F., 1985 (Box 7, Folder 741)
  - Tropp, Richard, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 742)
  - Trussell, Patricia M., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 743)
  - Trygstad, Carl, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 744)
  - Turbyfill, Charles, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 745)
  - Turtle, Robert, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 746)
  - Tyce, Gertrude, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 747)
  - Udenfriend, Sidney, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 748)
  - United Airlines, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 749)
  - Universal Oil Products, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 750)
  - Van Orden, L. S., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 751)
  - Van Woert, Melvin H. (AEC Contract), 1967-1982 (Box 7, Folder 752)
  - Van Woert, Melvin H., 1966-1969 (Box 7, Folder 753)
  - Vazques Garcia, D. Jose Antonio, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 754)
  - Velasco, Manuel, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 755)
  - Vere, Duncan, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 756)
  - Vesper Society, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 757)
  - Vinge, Daniel, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 758)
  - Vogel, Adolph, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 759)
  - Vozeh, Samuel, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 760)
  - Vugman, Itamar, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 761)
  - Waitkevicz, H. Joan, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 762)
  - Waldman, Robert, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 763)
  - Walker, J. M., 1975 (Box 7, Folder 764)
  - Walsh, Robert J., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 765)
  - Warren, Mike, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 766)
  - Wartik, Thomas, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 767)
  - Wasiowich, Elaine, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 768)
  - Waterbury Hospital, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 769)
  - Watkins, Elton, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 770)
  - Watts, Doris E., 1970-1976 (Box 7, Folder 771)
  - Waugaman, Paul, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 772)
  - Wayland, Sloan, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 773)
  - Weiner, Norman, 1970, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 774)
  - Weinhouse, Sidney, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 775)
  - Weintraub, Michael, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 776)
  - Weiss, Stephen, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 777)
  - Weissman, Lester, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 778)
  - Welch, Arnold D., 1965-1971 (Box 8, Folder 779)
  - Welch, Bruce L., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 780)
  - West, Geoffrey B., 1967 (Box 8, Folder 781)
  - Westling, H. and S. E. Lindell, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 782)
  - White, John W., 1981 (Box 8, Folder 783)
  - White, Stephen, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 784)
  - Whittemore, Ruth, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 785)
  - Who's Who in the United States, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 786)
  - Whysner, John A., 1978 (Box 8, Folder 787)
  - Wichmann, G. K., 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 788)
  - Wilfond, Ben, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 789)
  - Willard, H. N., 1969 (Box 8, Folder 790)
  - William S. Merrell Co., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 791)
  - Williams & Wilkins, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 792)
  - Williams, Carolyn, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 793)
  - Williams, Redford, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 794)
  - Wilson, Marjorie, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 795)
  - Wilson, Marjorie P., 1973 (Box 8, Folder 796)
  - Wilson, Thomas W., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 797)
  - Winik, Bruce, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 798)
  - Wood, Chester, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 799)
  - Wood, Jill, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 800)
  - Wood, Loring, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 801)
  - Wood (WI) Veterans Administration Hospital, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 802)
  - Woolsey, Frank, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 803)
  - Woolverton, John, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 804)
  - World Health Organization, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 805)
  - Yaffe, Sumner, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 806)
  - Yalow, Rosalyn, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 807)
  - Yamashiro, Koko, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 808)
  - Yeide, Harry, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 809)
  - Young, Gerald, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 810)
  - Zamchek, Norman, 1968-1978 (Box 8, Folder 811)
  - Zbar, Lisa, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 812)
  - Zollinger, Robert, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 813)
  - Chronological correspondence, 1997 February-August (Box 47, Folder 2-7)
- Office Files, 1962-1997; Series II
  Materials are arranged alphabetically by correspondents' last name, organization name, or journal title.
  This series contains primarily correspondence, as well as copies of papers and articles.
  - Aalestad, Hal, 1991-1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Abernathy, Gill, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Abrams, Donald, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Abrams, Natalie, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Abrams, William, 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Achem, Sami, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Adamski, Robert, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Addiction Research Center, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Adelberg, Edward, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - AIDS Advisory Committee (NIH), 1989-1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - AIDS Colloquium, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - AIDS Conference VIII, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - AIDS Fifth International Conference, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - AIDS, National Committee on, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - AIDS Program Advisory Committee (APAC) subcommittee, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
  - Alfano, Sandra, 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Allen, Ralph, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Allikmets, Lembit, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Almeder, Robert, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Alpha Omega Alpha, 1971-1982 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Amatruda, Thomas T., 1972-1985 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Ambani, Lalit, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Ameling, Ann, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - American Association for Clinical Investigation (ASCI), 1968-1989 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1966-1991 (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
  - American Cancer Society, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - American College of Cardiology (ACC), 1970-1975 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - American Heart Association, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - American Society for Clinical Pharmacology and Therapeutics (ASCPT) Government Affairs Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - American Society for Pharmacology and ExperimentalTherapeutics (ASPET), 1964-1975 (Box 9, Folder 32-33)
  - Ames, David, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Andrusko, Dave, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Angeletti, Fran, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Applied Research Ethics National Association (ARENA), 1985-1994 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Armstrong, Martine, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Arnstein, Robert, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Astrachan, Boris, 1977-1986 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Atkins, David, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Atkins, Elisha, 1977-1985 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Atkinson, Frank, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Austin Multi-IRB, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Baker, Bruce, 1987-1993 (Box 10, Folder 45-46)
  - Ball, John R., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Bankowski, Zbigniew, 1992-1995 (Box 10, Folder 48-50)
  - Banks, Richard, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Banner, Ron, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Barber, Bernard, 1979-1983 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Barinaga, Marcia, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Baron, Charles, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Barrnett, Russell J., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Bauer, Irmgard, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Baumgaertner, Michael, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Beeson, Diane, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Beeson, Paul B., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Beinfield, Malcolm, Undated (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Benander, Bruce, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Ben-Avie, Michael, Circa 1993 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Bender, Harvey A., 1974-1977 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Bennett, Donald, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Bentley-Cooper, Jo, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Benz, Edward J., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Berard, John, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Berchtold, Peter, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Berezuk, Gregory, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Bergen, Stanley, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Bern, Samuel, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Bernstein, Peter, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Bernstein, Robert, 1979-1985 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Bertino, Joseph R., 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Bianchine, Joseph, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Bioethics Reporter, 1982-1991 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Birdwhistell, Nan, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Bishop, J. Michael, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Bittar, E. Edward, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Blank, Robert, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Blick, Gary, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Bloom, Barry, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Bobrow, Samuel, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Boer, Alexa, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Bondeson, William, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Bondy, Philip K., 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Borak, Jonathan, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Bordeau, Edward, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Bosley, Warren, 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Bove, Joseph R., 1977-1985 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Bradie, Michael, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Braunwald, Eugene, 1972-1988 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Braybrooke, David, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Brecher, Edward M., 1979 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Brown, Jay, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Bryant, Jack, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Buckley, Berardine, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Burns, Vincent, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Burrell, Craig, 1975-1983 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Burroughs Welcome Fund, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Butler, Marcus, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Butler, Nancy Cunningham, 1988-1993 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Caccamo, Leonard, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Calderon, Rebecca L., 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Campbell, Courtney, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Canellakis, E. S., 1974 (Box 10, Folder 107)